modernyouth.com 2012-10-02

# ModernYouth.com | Privacy Policy

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us.

At Modern Youth, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by Modern Youth and how it is used. 

This privacy policy is subject to change and we advise you to review it periodically. All changes will be posted on this page for user review. Your use of this site, indicates acceptance of this privacy policy.

**Personal Information**  
Modern Youth, collects personally identifiable information from the visitors to our website only on a voluntary basis. Personal information including your name and email address may be collected during account registration. Other personal information we collect includes voluntary submissions (questions, answers, tips, etc.) that you post on our website. All of your submissions can be seen publicly, so we caution you to post responsibly.

All information you provide Modern Youth will be used for internal purposes and will not be sold or provided to third parties. Modern Youth uses this information to improve the content on our website, notify visitors about their account, and respond to visitor inquiries.

You have the ability to opt-out of all contact with Modern Youth by Unsubscribing from our website communications. Once you unsubscribe you will be taken off Modern Youth's mailing list. Click here to discontinue these communications.

**Log Files**  
Modern Youth makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes Internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks. We use this information, which does not identify users, to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

**Cookies**  
Modern Youth does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying your Web browser. However, if you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the site.

**Advertisers**  
We use third-party advertising companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies to determine how many times you've seen an advertisement. No personally identifiable information you give us is provided to them through cookies. Advertisers cannot personally identify you with the information on our website.

**Children's Online Privacy Protection Act**  
This website is directed to people over the age of 13. Our site operates in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, and will not knowingly collect or use personal information from anyone under 13 years of age.

**Contacting Us**  
We hope this privacy policy helped outline the types of information we collect, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. If you have any questions please contact us.
